pubarticles.com 2017-12-04

# Pubarticles.COM - Privacy Policy

Pubarticles.com ("pubarticles.com" or "we") are committed to protecting users and visitors ("users", "visitors" or "you") privacy. You have the right to know what information we collect, the purpose we collect your information, your information security, your information sharing with third party, etc. We reserve the right to modify pubarticles.com Privacy Policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time. 

**Acceptance of the Policy**

To access and use this site, you should agree the [Terms of Use](http://www.pubarticles.com/support/terms.html) and this Privacy Policy, including your information collection and processing. If you don't agree any term at this page, you mayn't use pubarticles.com.

**What Information We Collect from You?**

We collect two kinds information from our users and visitors, which are as following:  
**Personal Information Provided by User**  
After you register and set up an account on pubarticles.com, we can collect certain, such as your user name and e-mail address. All the personal information is provided by you voluntarily.   
Besides, we also support Facebook, Google, twitter, yahoo Login, and so you can use your existing account to access pubarticles.com. You must explicitly authorize Facebook, Google, twitter, yahoo to share your information with us when you first login to the Site.   
We clarify any Non-personal Information combined with Personal Information shall be regarded as Personal information. We will not collect any Personal Information from you without your approval.   
**Non-personal Information Collected Automatically**  
No matter you are a registered user or just a visitor, the Non-personal Information will be collected automatically. We list the details as following:  
a. Type of operation system (e.g Windows, Linux, android);  
b. Type of Browser (e.g. Explorer, Firefox, etc.);  
c. Your navigation path (the URLs of where you come to our site from, which of our pages you visit, and where you go as your leave);   
d. How long time you stay on certain page of pubarticles.com;   
e. Your computer's IP Address;   
f. The date and time you access the Site and pages you visit;   
g. The clicks, mouse movements on user content (e.g votes up and vote down). 

**Why We Collect Your Information?**

**Purpose of Collecting Personal Information:**  
a. Personalize your experience on pubarticles.com;  
b. Provide certain information and services for you which are only available to registered users (e.g such as follow, answer the questions);  
c. Identify you when conducting customer service operations;  
d. Contact you with proposals and tailored information;  
e. More User Generated Content, voluntarily supplied by the User for the purpose of public use and display.  
**Purpose of Collecting Non-personal Information:**  
a. users and visitors experience on pubarticles.com;  
b. Learn about users and visitors preferences and general trends on pubarticles.com;  
c. Better understand priorities and interests of potential users and partners to better suit their demands and increase efficiency of our sales and marketing processes;   
d. Administer pubartciles.com easily, and troubleshoot problems with our server.

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties?**

We may share your information with third parties in following situations:  
**Advertising partner:** Advertising partner delivers ads to users and visitors on pubarticles.com, and it is a reputable, independent ad server. We share Website usage information about you with advertising partner for targeting our advertisements on the website. We also use third party advertisers to display ads and collect information on the Website. Advertising partner may use your non-Personal Information in order to provide advertisements on the Website.   
**Third Party Services:** We contract with third parties to provide services to us or to you, such as providing marketing assistance, sending emails to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information, but will be demanded to only use them for these authorized business activities.   
**Business Transitions:** If we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, users information generally is one of the transferred business assets. So your personally information will be transferred to a bankruptcy trustee or debtor in possession and then to a subsequent purchaser.  
**Compliance and Safety:**  
a. To satisfy any applicable law, and to respond to legal requests or otherwise address written complaints of copyright infringement;   
b. To prevent potential crimes such as address fraud, or investigate persons;   
c. To enforce or apply [Privacy Policy](http://www.pubarticles.com/support/privacy-policy.html) or [Terms of Use](http://www.pubarticles.com/support/terms.html);  
d. To protect the rights, property, or safety of our Site, our users, or the general public.

**How Do We Protect Your Information Secure?**

We take commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical procedures to protect your Personally Information and other data from loss, misuse or alteration and to safeguard and secure the data you provide. But neither people nor security systems are foolproof, including encryption systems. In addition, people can commit intentional crimes, make mistakes or fail to follow policies. So we cannot guarantee its absolute security while using reasonable measures to protect your Personally Information. 

**Third Party Sites**

It is common to find third party websites while using pubarticles.com. Third party websites are independent sites, and we have no responsibility for their privacy practices. Please carefully read privacy policies and terms of use of third party websites.

**Changes and Updates of Privacy Policy**

We have the right to change or update our Policy at any time. And we wil give Policy's new effective date on the top of this page and the policy will take effect immediately.

**Contact Information**

If you have any question or advice, please contact us by sending email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
